<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://dongkyu-lee.info/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://dongkyu-lee.info/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-06-12T22:53:05+00:00</updated><id>https://dongkyu-lee.info/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">New Publication - Efficient seismic reliability and fragility analysis of lifeline networks using subset simulation</title><link href="https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2025/Paper3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Publication - Efficient seismic reliability and fragility analysis of lifeline networks using subset simulation"/><published>2025-03-07T16:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-07T16:30:00+00:00</updated><id>https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2025/Paper3</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2025/Paper3/"><![CDATA[<p>A journal paper, titled “Efficient seismic reliability and fragility analysis of lifeline networks using subset simulation” <a class="citation" href="#lee2025efficient">(Lee et al., 2025)</a>, was recently published in <em>Reliability Engineering &amp; System Safety</em>. The paper was co-authored by me, <a href="https://coezresearch.wpenginepowered.com/">Prof. Ziqi Wang</a> (UC Berkeley), and <a href="https://systemreliability.wordpress.com">Prof. Junho Song</a> (Seoul National University), thanks to the visiting research program with the support of Brain Korea 21 Global Research Fellowship (Ministry of Education, South Korea).</p> <p>The permanent link via DOI number of the paper is <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ress.2025.110947">HERE</a>. The full reference information is as follows.</p> <hr/> <blockquote> <p>Lee, D., Wang, Z., &amp; Song, J. (2025). <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ress.2025.110947">Efficient seismic reliability and fragility analysis of lifeline networks using subset simulation</a>. <em>Reliability Engineering &amp; System Safety</em>, Vol. 260, 110947.</p> </blockquote> <hr/> <p>This paper proposes two informative piecewise continuous limit-state functions (LSFs) for the reliability analysis of lifeline networks, thereby enabling the application of subset simulation (SS). Both LSF reformulations represent the same failure domain as the traditional binary LSF, while their function values at the safe domain differ; the first LSF quantifies the vulnerability of the most reliable path (RP) between the origin and destination nodes, whereas the other utilizes the shortest path (SP). The paper further proposes a specialized SS to generate network-level fragility curves by connecting intermediate failure events to the earthquake magnitude. The specialized SS can generate the network fragility curve in a single run. The sampling framework is extended to assess k-terminal or k-out-of-N reliability. The accuracy and efficiency of the proposed framework are tested and demonstrated by numerical examples using the Hamiltonian Monte Carlo-based SS (HMC-SS). The results confirm the accuracy and efficiency of the proposed network LSFs, as compared to other simulation-based methods directly applicable to binary LSFs. The RP-based LSF has higher accuracy, while the SP-based LSF requires less computation time.</p> <hr/> <h3 id="abstract">Abstract</h3> <p>Various simulation-based and analytical methods have been developed to evaluate the seismic fragilities of individual structures. However, the seismic safety and resilience of a community are substantially affected by network reliability, determined not only by component fragilities but also by network topology and commodity/information flows. However, seismic reliability analyses of networks often encounter significant challenges due to complex network topologies, interdependencies among ground motions, and low failure probabilities. This paper proposes to overcome these challenges by a variance-reduction method for network fragility analysis using subset simulation. The binary network limit-state function in the subset simulation is reformulated into more informative piecewise continuous functions. The proposed limit-state functions quantify the proximity of each sample to a potential network failure domain, thereby enabling the construction of specialized intermediate failure events, which can be utilized in subset simulation and other sequential Monte Carlo approaches. Moreover, by identifying an implicit relationship between intermediate failure events and seismic intensity, we propose a technique to obtain the entire network fragility curve with a single execution of specialized subset simulation. Numerical examples demonstrate that the proposed method can effectively evaluate system-level fragility for large-scale networks.</p> <swiper-container keyboard="true" navigation="true" pagination="true" pagination-clickable="true" pagination-dynamic-bullets="true" rewind="true"> <swiper-slide> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news3_1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news3_1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news3_1-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news3_1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </swiper-slide> <swiper-slide> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news3_2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news3_2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news3_2-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news3_2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </swiper-slide> </swiper-container> <div class="caption"> Samples obtained from the (a) entire domain; (b) first subset; and (c) second subset using RP or SP. </div> <div class="row"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news3_3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news3_3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news3_3-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news3_3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" title="example image" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> (a) Comparison of generated seismic fragility curves of San Jose highway bridge network; and (b) multi-state network fragility curves obtained by specialized HMC-SS. </div> <hr/> <h3 id="acknowledgment">Acknowledgment</h3> <ul> <li>This work is supported by the Korea Agency for Infrastructure Technology Advancement (KAIA) grant funded by the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure and Transport (RS-2021-KA163162). The first author is also supported by the Basic Science Research Program through the National Research Foundation of Korea (NRF) funded by the Ministry of Education (RS-2024-00408907). The third author is also supported by the Institute of Construction and Environmental Engineering at Seoul National University.</li> </ul> <hr/>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Paper"/><category term="Publication"/><category term="NetworkReliability"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publication]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Publication - Risk-informed operation and maintenance of complex lifeline systems using parallelized multi-agent deep Q-network</title><link href="https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2023/Paper2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Publication - Risk-informed operation and maintenance of complex lifeline systems using parallelized multi-agent deep Q-network"/><published>2023-11-01T16:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T16:30:00+00:00</updated><id>https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2023/Paper2</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2023/Paper2/"><![CDATA[<p>A journal paper, titled “Risk-informed operation and maintenance of complex lifeline systems using parallelized multi-agent deep Q-network” <a class="citation" href="#lee2023risk">(Lee &amp; Song*, 2023)</a>, was recently published in <em>Reliability Engineering &amp; System Safety</em>. The paper was co-authored by me and <a href="https://systemreliability.wordpress.com/">Prof. Junho Song</a> (Seoul National University).</p> <p>Through the support by Seoul National University, the paper was published as an Open Access article, and thus downloadable for free. The permanent link via DOI number of the paper is <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ress.2023.109512">HERE</a>. The full reference information is as follows.</p> <hr/> <blockquote> <p>Lee, D., &amp; Song, J. (2023). <a href="https://snu.elsevierpure.com/en/publications/risk-informed-operation-and-maintenance-of-complex-lifeline-syste">Risk-informed operation and maintenance of complex lifeline systems using parallelized multi-agent deep Q-network</a>. <em>Reliability Engineering &amp; System Safety</em>. Vol. 239, 109512.</p> </blockquote> <hr/> <p>This paper proposes a multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL) framework, called parallelized multi-agent deep Q-network (PM-DQN), for efficient risk-informed operation and management (O&amp;M) of lifeline systems. PM-DQN introduces a divide-and-conquer strategy with community detection to explore the optimal policy with low computational cost. The strength of the proposed algorithm is further enhanced by hyperparameter tuning and periodic synchronization combined with parallel processing. The applications to the multi-state general system and the realistic gas distribution system successfully demonstrate the performance and advantages of the proposed method. In both examples, the proposed method outperforms conventional O&amp;M methods and other MARL-based methods in terms of computational time and expected life-cycle cost. Furthermore, the second example demonstrates that the proposed framework of agent deployment and periodic synchronization of multiple processors can be applied to other DRL methods.</p> <hr/> <h3 id="abstract">Abstract</h3> <p>Lifeline systems such as transportation and water distribution networks may deteriorate with age, raising the risk of system failure or degradation. Thus, system-level sequential decision-making is essential to address the problem cost-effectively while minimizing the potential loss. Researchers have proposed to assess the risk of lifeline systems using Markov decision processes (MDPs) to identify a risk-informed operation and maintenance (O&amp;M) policy. In complex systems with many components, however, it is potentially intractable to find MDP solutions because the numbers of states and action spaces increase exponentially. This paper proposes a multi-agent deep reinforcement learning framework, termed parallelized multi-agent deep Q-network (PM-DQN), to overcome the curse of dimensionality. The proposed method takes a divide-and-conquer strategy, in which multiple subsystems are identified by community detection, and each agent learns to achieve the O&amp;M policy of the corresponding subsystem. The agents establish policies to minimize the decentralized cost of the cluster unit, including the factorized cost. Such learning processes occur simultaneously in several parallel units, and the trained policies are periodically synchronized with the best ones, thereby improving the master policy. Numerical examples demonstrate that the proposed method outperforms baseline policies, including conventional maintenance schemes and the subsystem-level optimal policy.</p> <swiper-container keyboard="true" navigation="true" pagination="true" pagination-clickable="true" pagination-dynamic-bullets="true" rewind="true"> <swiper-slide> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news7_2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news7_2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news7_2-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news7_2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </swiper-slide> <swiper-slide> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news7_1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news7_1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news7_1-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news7_1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </swiper-slide> <swiper-slide> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news7_3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news7_3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news7_3-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news7_3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </swiper-slide> <swiper-slide> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news7_4-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news7_4-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news7_4-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news7_4.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </swiper-slide> </swiper-container> <hr/> <h3 id="acknowledgment">Acknowledgment</h3> <ul> <li>This first author is supported by the National Research Foundation of Korea grant funded by the Korea government (MSIT) (No. RS-2022-00144434). The corresponding author is supported by the Institute of Construction and Environmental Engineering at Seoul National University.</li> </ul> <hr/>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Paper"/><category term="Publication"/><category term="DeepLearning"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publication]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Visit to University of California, Berkeley</title><link href="https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2022/UCB/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Visit to University of California, Berkeley"/><published>2022-10-28T16:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-28T16:30:00+00:00</updated><id>https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2022/UCB</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2022/UCB/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="details-of-the-work-at-university-of-california-berkeley-uc-berkeley">Details of the work at University of California, Berkeley (UC Berkeley)</h2> <p>I have started my three-month visiting research program at UC Berkeley, USA, with the support of Brain Korea 21 Global Research Fellowship (Ministry of Education, South Korea). During my stay at UC Berkeley, I collaborate with the host, <a href="https://coezresearch.wpenginepowered.com/">Prof. Ziqi Wang</a>.</p> <p>As a first step, we have developed a new advanced sampling-based method for reliability analysis of complex infrastructure networks <a class="citation" href="#lee2025efficient">(Lee et al., 2025)</a>. The permanent link via DOI number of the paper is <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ress.2025.110947">HERE</a>. The full reference information is as follows.</p> <hr/> <blockquote> <p>Lee, D., Wang, Z., &amp; Song, J. (2025). <a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ress.2025.110947">Efficient seismic reliability and fragility analysis of lifeline networks using subset simulation</a>. <em>Reliability Engineering &amp; System Safety</em>, 260: 110947.</p> </blockquote> <hr/> <p>This paper proposes two informative limit-state functions (LSFs) to reformulate the traditional binary LSF for two-terminal reliability analysis of lifeline networks, thereby making the application of subset simulation (SS) possible. The first LSF quantifies the vulnerability of the most reliable path between the origin and destination nodes, whereas the other utilizes the shortest path. Both LSF reformulations represent the same failure domain as the original binary limit-sate function, while their function values at the safe domain differ. Moreover, a specialized SS is developed to generate network-level fragility curves by connecting intermediate failure events to the earthquake magnitude. As a result, the specialized SS can generate the network fragility curve in a single run. Furthermore, the sampling framework is successfully extended to assess k-terminal or k-out-of-N reliability. The accuracy and efficiency of the proposed framework are tested and demonstrated by numerical examples using the Hamiltonian Monte Carlo-based SS (HMC-SS). The results confirm the accuracy and efficiency of the proposed network LSFs, compared to other simulation-based methods directly applicable to binary LSFs. The first LSF generally has higher accuracy, while the second requires lower computation time.</p> <swiper-container keyboard="true" navigation="true" pagination="true" pagination-clickable="true" pagination-dynamic-bullets="true" rewind="true"> <swiper-slide> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news3_1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news3_1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news3_1-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news3_1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </swiper-slide> <swiper-slide> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news3_2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news3_2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news3_2-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news3_2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </swiper-slide> </swiper-container> <div class="caption"> Samples obtained from the (a) entire domain; (b) first subset; and (c) second subset using RP or SP </div> <div class="row"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news3_3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news3_3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news3_3-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news3_3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" title="example image" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> (a) Comparison of generated seismic fragility curves of San Jose highway bridge network; and (b) multi-state network fragility curves obtained by specialized HMC-SS. </div> <hr/>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Visiting"/><category term="Visiting"/><category term="Fellowship"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visiting]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Publication - Multi-scale seismic reliability assessment of networks by centrality-based selective recursive decomposition algorithm</title><link href="https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2021/Paper1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Publication - Multi-scale seismic reliability assessment of networks by centrality-based selective recursive decomposition algorithm"/><published>2021-07-10T16:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-07-10T16:30:00+00:00</updated><id>https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2021/Paper1</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2021/Paper1/"><![CDATA[<p>A journal paper, titled “Multi-scale seismic reliability assessment of networks by centrality-based selective recursive decomposition algorithm” <a class="citation" href="#lee2021multi">(Lee &amp; Song*, 2021)</a>, was recently published in <em>Earthquake Engineering &amp; Structural Dynamics</em>. The paper was co-authored by me and <a href="https://systemreliability.wordpress.com/">Prof. Junho Song</a> (Seoul National University).</p> <p>The permanent link via DOI number of the paper is <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/eqe.3447">HERE</a>. The full reference information is as follows.</p> <hr/> <blockquote> <p>Lee, D., &amp; Song, J. (2021). <a href="https://snu.elsevierpure.com/en/publications/multi-scale-seismic-reliability-assessment-of-networks-by-central">Multi-scale seismic reliability assessment of networks by centrality-based selective recursive decomposition algorithm</a>. <em>Earthquake Engineering &amp; Structural Dynamics</em>. Vol. 50, 2174-2194.</p> </blockquote> <hr/> <p>This paper proposed a new non-simulation-based algorithm to analyze the post-hazard network connectivity promptly but accurately. To this end, two algorithms were developed and utilized: (1) centrality-based selective recursive decomposition algorithm (CS-RDA), and (2) edge-betweenness algorithm. First, CS-RDA finds the most reliable path between an origin and destination (O/D) node pair, and decompose the network into subgraphs by removing the nodes in the path in order of network centrality. The O/D connectivity and its probability in subgraphs are recursively assessed until the width of bounds on the O/D connectivity converge to a certain level. In addition, a multi-scale analysis utilizing edge-betweenness algorithm enables CS-RDA to overcome the computational limitation in large-scale networks without compromising accuracy. The numerical examples including a hypothetical network and highway bridge networks in San Jose and San Diego demonstrate the performance and merits of the proposed methods.</p> <div class="row"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news8_1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news8_1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news8_1-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news8_1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" title="example image" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Flowchart of the recursive decomposition algorithm </div> <hr/> <h3 id="abstract">Abstract</h3> <p>As lifeline networks such as transportation or electricity networks in modern societies are intricately interlocked, a small number of components damaged by natural or man-made disasters can have a great impact on network performance. For this reason, it is essential to assure the capability of rapid assessment of network reliability to make prompt follow-up measures. Despite the rapid development of various algorithms and computing power, the capability is still limited due to computational cost for analyzing the connectivity of a single origin and destination (O/D) node pair in large-scale networks. Therefore, this paper introduces a new algorithm utilizing network centrality, termed “centrality-based selective recursive decomposition algorithm” (CS-RDA). By preferentially decomposing the node which is most likely to belong to the min-cut identified based on the betweenness centrality, the convergence of the bounds on the O/D connectivity can be expedited significantly. This paper also introduces a new multi-scale analysis approach termed “edge-betweenness algorithm.” The algorithm groups components such that its modularity is maximized, by sequentially removing edges that have the highest level of betweenness centrality. As a result, the reliability of large-scale networks can be accurately evaluated in a short time owing to the reduced complexity of the simplified network. The proposed methods are successfully demonstrated by a hypothetical network example, the highway bridge networks in San Jose and San Diego in California, USA.</p> <swiper-container keyboard="true" navigation="true" pagination="true" pagination-clickable="true" pagination-dynamic-bullets="true" rewind="true"> <swiper-slide> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news8_2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news8_2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news8_2-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news8_2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </swiper-slide> <swiper-slide> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news8_3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news8_3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news8_3-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news8_3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </swiper-slide> </swiper-container> <hr/> <h3 id="acknowledgment">Acknowledgment</h3> <ul> <li>This work is supported by a grant from Smart Civil Infrastructure Research Program funded by the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure and Transport (21SCIP-B146946-04).</li> </ul> <hr/>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Paper"/><category term="Publication"/><category term="NetworkReliability"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publication]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Visit to University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign</title><link href="https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2019/UIUC/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Visit to University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign"/><published>2019-12-23T16:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-23T16:30:00+00:00</updated><id>https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2019/UIUC</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dongkyu-lee.info/blog/2019/UIUC/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="details-of-the-work-at-national-center-for-supercomputing-applications-ncsa">Details of the work at National Center for Supercomputing Applications (NCSA)</h2> <p>From December 23, 2019, Youngjun Kwon and I have started our two-month research visit at the NCSA at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign (UIUC) with the support of the EDRC Research Intern Program (Ministry of Trade, Industry and Energy, S. Korea). During the visit, we study the ongoing research of the institution, called <a href="https://incore.ncsa.illinois.edu/">Interdependent Networked Community Resilience Modeling Environment</a> (IN-CORE), with the help of Dr. Jong Lee and Chen Wang.</p> <h2 id="application">Application</h2> <p>Seismic damage analysis in Seoul, S. Korea</p> <div class="row justify-content-sm-center"> <div class="col-sm-7 mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news2_1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news2_1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news2_1-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news2_1.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" title="example image" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> <div class="col-sm-5 mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news2_3-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news2_3-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news2_3-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news2_3.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" title="example image" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> (a) Buildings in the target area; and (b) spatial distribution of the buildings' seismic failure probabilities (return period: 1,000 years) </div> <div class="row"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/news/news2_2-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/news/news2_2-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/news/news2_2-1400.webp 1400w," type="image/webp" sizes="95vw"/> <img src="/assets/img/news/news2_2.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" title="example image" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Distribution of building failure probabilities according to earthquake's return periods </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Visiting"/><category term="Visiting"/><category term="Fellowship"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visiting]]></summary></entry></feed>